[Music]
hi guys
welcome back to another informative
video where we discuss things about
saving investing stock market
and a lot of practical tips that you can
use to improve your way of living
today's video will have another
insurance vol
review so and i'm going to
upload the videos about insurances and
this is another product feature
um just a disclaimer insurance products
or any investment products
why not preference
preferences
investment plan whether it's for
insurance for vol uitf
but this is me sharing my experience and
third and last tip risk level
risk level low moderate or high
teenagers
so this is a product review by fwd
so bahamas
fwd my goal for this year is
insurance unfortunately there
was an incident that happened early this
year nana postponed or
hiding
because a night before
insurance
insurance provider and i want to be
transparent to any agent
um
information
[Music]
i'll go with another provider which is
fwd
saudi in my recent videos you have seen
that i got my car with security bank
security bank and fwd i think they've
been partners with
um each other since 2014. you didn't
have an agent called but they are an
entity here in the philippines since
2013.
so in terms of apprehension and
preference
partner usually established natala galax
sun life in prolife
since this is your money preference
plays a huge factor in your
decision-making process
in my case
of the agency i used to have an
internship program with
so don't first
during that event but other than that
never knew
my friends
but to those people who would like to
check fwd la luna
lagging that they decline it's it pays
to look at other
um insurance providers because you'll
never know
if you have seen some of the videos that
i have uploaded
uh pertaining to insurance plans policy
owner
perry life insured in our case is
[Music]
so it's good for seven years seven years
to pay sha at an amount
for the seven year plan
is about six thousand eight hundred
seventy five good for seven years so
monthly ambabaya
na policy owner would be six thousand
eight hundred seventy five
mashallah because in some other konamero
six thousand this is for five hundred
thousand coverage
six thousand eight hundred seventy five
majoring in the uncle for saving
again
seven um years that's five hundred
thousand some assured
tapos safety approach a health prolife
take
that's until age one hundred so isa
naman
yung right there's nothing up to age 75.
so ayan so the basic premium
is forty thousand pesos the
supplementary benefits
premium in total would be thirty seven
thousand three hundred the total annual
premium is seventy seven thousand three
hundred twenty
so mejo i know nothing i multiply
nothing
[Music]
that benefits same goes it's for a 10.
so me increase
benefit would be one hundred forty one
thousand
kapagdam and eight percent that's one
fifty six thousand
ten percent that's one hundred sixty
four thousand dollar man cycle fifth
year don't say that benefit yeah it's
it's still the same
what i can note here though
that benefit benefits
but definitely market is really
fluctuating so
your money is already at 253 000 if it's
at eight percent
don't worry for post kotoha 330 000 and
ten percent three seventy five so yeah
on the tenth year walang bhagava bag on
your death benefit
do not i say 15 years
15 so on the 15th that would
amount to 287 tapos eight percent is 480
at 603 per thousand
ten percent sodium per hour
three thousand eight hundred for ten
years
three thousand eight hundred tenant
safety pro
nissan rider don s
that is seven thousand six hundred tapos
eight percent ninety thousand ten
percent it's at
um ninety four thousand capacity
at four percent two sixty thousand
capacity
[Music]
another process with true life
you can always go to other providers
like fwd
my axa my
this is like a personal take planner i
would want to go to an institution
independent partnerships i don't know
why i feel like
they are weak when they do partnership
why
but again don't come after me it's just
my own opinion
that's why
sun life because those entities
and they've been good in that um in that
game for the longest time
i'm not saying fwd is not good but if
you are a practical person like me
become approved approve at this moment
life insured you
3 800 i think it's a good amount
so i would ask them maybe if they can
close it to 300 and lower down the
benefits
of somebody
and always make sure that you have a
backup plan
you have your financial goals if this is
really what you want
investment and for you to get an
insurance or vul it's already a good
step
for you at pero hondika paradi keep on
watching more videos read more
articles about insurance as para kapag
redi
i i hope i was able to share another
product feature napoleon you try
and insert all the quotations
thank you for watching bye
[Music]
you